A Guide to the Winthrop Rockefeller Foundation records FA248
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Grants, 1972-2001; 2 (Reel 15, Frame 203)
  - Education Mini-Grants, 1995-1998; 3 (Reel 111, Frame 1042)
    - Little Rock School District, 96-151, 1996-1997 (Reel 113, Frame 75)
    - Little Rock School District, 97-11, 1997-1998 (Reel 113, Frame 118)
    - Lonoke School District, 96-145, 1996-1997 (Reel 113, Frame 149)
    - Magnet Cove Public Schools, 97-11, 1996-1997 (Reel 113, Frame 181)
    - Malvern Special School District, 96-60, 1996-1997 (Reel 113, Frame 226)
    - Monticello School District, 96-95, 1996-1997 (Reel 113, Frame 299)
    - Monticello School District, 96-141, 1996 (Reel 113, Frame 346)
    - Nettleton School District, 96-135, 1996-1997 (Reel 113, Frame 381)
    - Nettleton School District, 96-152, 1996-1997 (Reel 113, Frame 421)
    - North Little Rock School District, 96-76, 1995-1997 (Reel 113, Frame 459)
    - North Little Rock School District, 96-103, 1996-1997 (Reel 113, Frame 504)
    - Oden School District, 96-33, 1995-1996 (Reel 113, Frame 542)
    - Osceola School District, 96-143, 1996-1997 (Reel 113, Frame 581)
    - Paragould School District, Formerly Known As North East Arkansas School District, 96-96, 1995-1997 (Reel 113, Frame 622)
    - Pine Bluff School District, 96-93, 1996 (Reel 113, Frame 680)
    - Plainview-Rover Public Schools, 96-105, 1996-1997 (Reel 113, Frame 717)
    - Pulaski County Special School District, 96-15, 1995-1997 (Reel 113, Frame 754)
    - Pulaski County Special School District, 96-109, 1996-1997 (Reel 113, Frame 798)
    - Pulaski County Special School District, 96-140, 1996-1997 (Reel 113, Frame 839)
    - Pulaski County Special School District, 97-3, 1996-1998 (Reel 113, Frame 881)
    - Rogers Public Schools, 96-23, 1996 (Reel 113, Frame 913)
    - Russellville School District, 96-13, 1995-1996 (Reel 113, Frame 942)
    - Russellville School District, 96-120, 1996-1997 (Reel 113, Frame 987)
    - Russellville School District, 97-8, 1997-1998 (Reel 113, Frame 1026)
    - Searcy School District, 96-101, 1996 (Reel 113, Frame 1053)
    - Sloan-Hendrix School District, 96-112, 1996-1997 (Reel 113, Frame 1084)
    - South Mississippi County School District, 96-72, 1996 (Reel 113, Frame 1120)
    - South side School District, 96-56, 1996 (Reel 113, Frame 1161)
    - Springdale School District, 96-59, 1996-1997 (Reel 114, Frame 1)
    - Springdale School District, 96-129, 1996-1997 (Reel 114, Frame 47)
    - Stamps Public Schools, 96-147, 1996-1997 (Reel 114, Frame 91)
    - Star City Public Schools, 96-110, 1996-1997 (Reel 114, Frame 134)
    - Texarkana Arkansas School District, 97-6, 1997 (Reel 114, Frame 165)
    - Viola Public Schools, 96-61, 1995-1997 (Reel 114, Frame 189)
    - Walnut Ridge Public Schools, 97-15, 1997 (Reel 114, Frame 234)
    - Watson Chapel School District, 97-5, 1996-1997 (Reel 114, Frame 268)
    - West Memphis School District, 96-114, 1995-1997 (Reel 114, Frame 293)
    - Westside Consolidated School District, 96-149, 1996-1997 (Reel 114, Frame 333)
    - Wickes Public Schools, 97-13, 1996-1998 (Reel 114, Frame 365)
    - Witts Springs School District, 96-104, 1996-1997 (Reel 114, Frame 388)
    - Yellville-Summit School District, 97-10, 1997-1998 (Reel 114, Frame 432)
  - Arkansas Issues, 1972-1996; 4 (Reel 114, Frame 457)
    Addressing issues that are important to Arkansas in the areas of: economics, education, and the environment.
    - Economics (Reel 114, Frame 458)
      - An Agenda for Tax Reform in Arkansas, 1983-1987 (Reel 114, Frame 459)
      - Arkansas State Revenues, 1988-1989 (Reel 114, Frame 729)
      - Capital Availability, 1983-1984 (Reel 114, Frame 845)
      - Coalition for Fair Taxes, 1983 (Reel 115, Frame 1)
      - Community Planning/Enterprise Zones, 1994 (Reel 115, Frame 14)
      - Corporate Income Tax, 1983-1984 (Reel 115, Frame 40)
      - Economic Development in Arkansas, Obstacles, 1982-1987 (Reel 115, Frame 260)
      - Economic Development in Arkansas, 12 Obstacles, Legislative Report Card, 1979-1987 (Reel 115, Frame 542)
      - Financial Management Workshops, 1994-1995 (Reel 115, Frame 730)
      - Housing: Low to Moderate Income, Piece of the Puzzle, Phase I and II, 1989-1991 (Reel 115, Frame 734)
      - Housing Initiative Documentation, 1992-1994 (Reel 115, Frame 748)
      - Increasing Philanthropy in Arkansas, 1990-1991 (Reel 115, Frame 764)
      - Individual Income Tax, 1984-1985 (Reel 115, Frame 778)
      - Leveraging Study, Original Proposal-, 1990-1991 (Reel 115, Frame 882)
      - Leveraging Study, Report-Study, 1991 (Reel 116, Frame 1)
      - Micro-Loan Funds, Vendor Invoice Files, 1995-1996 (Reel 116, Frame 264)
      - Property Tax, 1983-1984 (Reel 116, Frame 273)
      - Property Taxes in Arkansas, 1981-1982 (Reel 116, Frame 592)
      - Rural Profile of Arkansas, 1993 (Reel 116, Frame 694)
      - Sales Tax, 1983-1985 (Reel 116, Frame 701)
      - Sales Tax, Newspaper Clippings-Vendor Invoice Files, 1983-1986 (Reel 116, Frame 841)
      - Second Look, Housing Arena, Vendor Invoice Files, 1996 (Reel 116, Frame 1118)
      - Severance Tax, 1982-1983 (Reel 117, Frame 1)
      - Tax Overview, 1982-1985 (Reel 117, Frame 95)
      - Tax Overview, Newspaper Clippings, 1983-1987 (Reel 117, Frame 307)
    - Education (Reel 117, Frame 408)
      - AETN Foundation, Arkansas Educational Telecommunication Network Foundation, Arkansas/Soviet Union Student Exchange, 1989 (Reel 117, Frame 409)
      - Amendment 59, 1990-1992 (Reel 117, Frame 414)
      - Arkansas School Reform Study, Professional Services Agreement, 1987 1985-1987 (Reel 117, Frame 597)
      - Arkansas School Reform Study, 1988-1989 (Reel 117, Frame 860)
      - Arkansas School Reform Study, Financial, 1986-1988 (Reel 118, Frame 1)
      - Arkansas School Reform Study, Newspaper Clippings-Vendor Invoice Files, 1985-1989 (Reel 118, Frame 211)
      - Break the Mold, Process Observer, 1993-1995 (Reel 118, Frame 275)
      - Education Accountability, 1977 (Reel 118, Frame 322)
      - Edukashun: The High Cost of Failure, 1988-1989 (Reel 118, Frame 347)
      - Higher Education, Vendor Invoice Files, 1983 (Reel 118, Frame 523)
      - Home Visit Manual, 1992-1994 (Reel 118, Frame 531)
      - The Institute for Educational Leadership, Incorporated, 1988 (Reel 118, Frame 540)
      - MPT Study, Maximum Performance Test, 1990-1992 (Reel 118, Frame 630)
      - Parent Involvement Manual, 1993-1994 (Reel 118, Frame 1001)
      - Public Education: Second Crisis in Little Rock, Follow-up, Conflict Resolution, 1987-1989 (Reel 119, Frame 1)
      - Reading Recovery, Vendor Invoice Files, 1994 (Reel 119, Frame 344)
      - Video Distribution, Edutainment, Vendor Invoice Files, 1988-1993 (Reel 119, Frame 347)
    - Environment (Reel 119, Frame 366)
      - AETN, Arkansas Educational Television Network, Land Use Documentary, 1984-1986 (Reel 119, Frame 367)
      - An Assessment of the Production Base for Agriculture: Environmental Quality, Natural Resources and Technologies for the 21st Century, 1993 (Reel 119, Frame 459)
      - The Conservation Foundation, Vendor Invoice Files, 1984 (Reel 119, Frame 461)
      - Environmental and Economic Concerns Involving Forest Practices, 1980-1989 (Reel 119, Frame 465)
      - Groundwater, Vendor Invoice Files, 1985 (Reel 119, Frame 810)
      - Land as a Resource, 1983-1984 (Reel 119, Frame 817)
      - Land Use Issues, 1972-1987 (Reel 119, Frame 837)
      - Recycling and Integrated Solid Waste Management, 1987-1991 (Reel 120, Frame 1)
      - Toxic Substances, Original Proposal-Professional Services Agreement, 1984-1986 (Reel 120, Frame 357)
      - Toxic Substances, 1984-1987 (Reel 120, Frame 492)
      - Wastewater Management, University of Arkansas, 1975-1980 (Reel 120, Frame 641)
      - Water for Arkansas' Future, 1983-1989 (Reel 120, Frame 975)
      - Water Issues, Grant Agreement-Correspondence, 1980-1983 (Reel 121, Frame 1)
      - Water Issues, Newspaper Clippings-Vendor Invoice Files, 1981-1988 (Reel 121, Frame 462)
    - General Issues (Reel 121, Frame 618)
      - Arkansas Corporate Connection, 1994-1995 (Reel 121, Frame 619)
      - Arkansas Citizen Participation, Vendor Invoice Files, 1994 (Reel 121, Frame 622)
      - Arkansas Report, KTHV, Television Pilot, 1986-1988 (Reel 121, Frame 637)
      - At-Risk Program Documentation, 1992-1995 (Reel 121, Frame 947)
      - Block Grant Planning, Vendor Invoice Files, 1995 (Reel 121, Frame 956)
      - Champion Communities Initiative, Vendor Invoice Files, 1996 (Reel 121, Frame 959)
      - Commercial National Bank, 1976 (Reel 121, Frame 963)
      - Communication Workshops for Non-Profits, 1989-1992 (Reel 121, Frame 974)
      - Community Development Corporation Handbook and Network Development, 1992-1994 (Reel 122, Frame 1)
      - The Dream... The Mission, Video of the Winthrop Rockefeller Foundation, Vendor Invoice Files, 1990-1991 (Reel 122, Frame 12)
      - Five Year Plan, Issued Grants, 1981 (Reel 122, Frame 20)
      - Grassroots Leadership, 1988-1994 (Reel 122, Frame 229)
      - International Community Leadership Conference, Reunion, Vendor Invoice Files, 1983-1984 (Reel 122, Frame 512)
      - Martin Luther King, Jr. Commission, Vendor Invoice Files, 1994 (Reel 122, Frame 524)
      - Political Activity of the Religious Right in the 's, Vendor Invoice Files, 1990-1994 (Reel 122, Frame 536)
      - Public Policy Associates, Incorporated, Chapter 1 Study, Vendor Invoice Files, 1995 (Reel 122, Frame 538)
      - Public Policy Conference, 1983 (Reel 122, Frame 546)
      - Public Policy Journal, 1980-1982 (Reel 122, Frame 795)
      - Public Servant/Positive Role Model, 1993 (Reel 122, Frame 922)
      - Transition of the Clinton Administration to the Presidency, 1993 (Reel 122, Frame 927)
      - Undoing Racism and Organizing, Vendor Invoice Files, 1993-1995 (Reel 122, Frame 974)
      - Winthrop Rockefeller Foundation Networking Conference, Vendor Invoice Files, 1991-1995 (Reel 122, Frame 991)
      - Youth Issues Assessment, Vendor Invoice Files, 1994-1995 (Reel 122, Frame 1095)
      - Youth Programs and Services, Inventory, 1993-1995 (Reel 123, Frame 1)
    - Inactive Issues (Reel 123, Frame 208)
      - Arkansas Tax Policy, 1985 (Reel 123, Frame 209)
      - Fast Forward: A Video Workshop for Community Change, 1984 (Reel 123, Frame 214)
      - Tax Wrap-Up Issue, 1984-1987 (Reel 123, Frame 247)
      - Unborn Child Agreement, 1984 (Reel 123, Frame 229)
      - University of Arkansas at Little Rock, Public History Program Intern, 1984 (Reel 123, Frame 235)
      - Well Water Contamination, 1984 (Reel 123, Frame 243)
    - Miscellaneous (Reel 123, Frame 255)
      - Contingency Fund, 1984-1995 (Reel 123, Frame 256)
  - Southern Development Bancorporation, Incorporated, 1977-1998; 5 (Reel 123, Frame 272)
    Southern Development Bancorporation, Incorporated, is a development bank holding company that focuses on rural economic development.
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 1988 August 24 (Reel 123, Frame 273)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 1988 November 2 (Reel 123, Frame 341)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 1989 May 18 (Reel 123, Frame 391)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 1990 November 20 (Reel 123, Frame 451)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 1994 February 9 (Reel 123, Frame 547)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 1994 May 18 (Reel 123, Frame 695)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 1994 September 22 (Reel 123, Frame 822)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 1994 December 22 (Reel 123, Frame 957)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 1995 February 8 (Reel 123, Frame 1066)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 1996 February 13 (Reel 124, Frame 1)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 1996 June 24 (Reel 124, Frame 68)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 1996 August 14 (Reel 124, Frame 85)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 1997 August 21 (Reel 124, Frame 88)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 1997 October 1 (Reel 124, Frame 191)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 1997 December (Reel 124, Frame 510)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 1998 February 26 (Reel 124, Frame 610)
    - Shorebank Corporation, Board of Directors Meeting, 1990 April 28 (Reel 124, Frame 796)
    - Shorebank Corporation, Board of Directors Meeting, 1990 October 20 (Reel 124, Frame 1014)
    - Shorebank Corporation, Board of Directors Meeting, 1994 October 15 (Reel 125, Frame 1)
    - Shorebank Corporation, Board of Directors Meeting, 1995 April 21 (Reel 125, Frame 135)
    - Capital Call, Supplemental Information, 1987 December 9 (Reel 125, Frame 403)
    - Chronological Files, 1983 (Reel 125, Frame 699)
    - Chronological Files, 1984 (Reel 125, Frame 857)
    - Chronological Files, 1985 (Reel 125, Frame 948)
    - Chronological Files, 1986 January-March (Reel 126, Frame 1)
    - Chronological Files, 1986 April-June (Reel 126, Frame 354)
    - Chronological Files, 1986 July-September (Reel 126, Frame 715)
    - Chronological Files, 1986 October-December 1986-1987 (Reel 126, Frame 986)
    - Chronological Files, 1986 January-1987 March (Reel 127, Frame 1)
    - Chronological Files, 1987 April-June (Reel 127, Frame 231)
    - Chronological Files, 1987 July-September (Reel 127, Frame 553)
    - Chronological Files, 1987 October (Reel 127, Frame 479)
    - Chronological Files, 1987 November-December (Reel 128, Frame 1)
    - Chronological Files, 1988 January-March (Reel 128, Frame 264)
    - Chronological Files, 1988 April-June (Reel 128, Frame 625)
    - Chronological Files, 1988 July-December (Reel 128, Frame 872)
    - Chronological Files, 1989-1990 (Reel 129, Frame 1)
    - Chronological Files, 1991 (Reel 129, Frame 279)
    - Chronological Files, 1992 (Reel 129, Frame 410)
    - Chronological Files, 1993 (Reel 129, Frame 564)
    - Chronological Files, 1994 (Reel 129, Frame 635)
    - Chronological Files, 1995 January-March (Reel 129, Frame 806)
    - Chronological Files, 1995 April-December (Reel 130, Frame 1)
    - Chronological Files, 1996 January-March (Reel 130, Frame 390)
    - Chronological Files, 1996 April (Reel 130, Frame 571)
    - Chronological Files, 1996 May-December (Reel 130, Frame 906)
    - Chronological Files, 1997 January-March (Reel 131, Frame 1)
    - Chronological Files, 1997 April-August (Reel 131, Frame 350)
    - Chronological Files, 1997 August-December (Reel 131, Frame 532)
    - Chronological Files, 1998 (Reel 131, Frame 760)
    - Crane and Associates, 1987 (Reel 131, Frame 833)
    - Newspaper Clippings, 1986-1988 (Reel 131, Frame 848)
    - Strategic Plan, 1993 (Reel 131, Frame 978)
    - Strategic Plan, 1994 (Reel 132, Frame 1)
    - Strategic Plan, 1995 (Reel 132, Frame 142)
    - Strategic Plan, 1996 (Reel 132, Frame 212)
    - Subscription Agreement, 1997-1998 (Reel 132, Frame 376)
    - Winthrop Rockefeller Foundation Ad Hoc Committee, 1996-1997 (Reel 132, Frame 405)
- Financial, 1974-2000; 3 (Reel 132, Frame 675)
  - Budgets and Ledgers, 1974-2000; 1 (Reel 132, Frame 676)
    The financial material of the Winthrop Rockefeller Foundation.
    - Ernst and Whinney Budget Format Instructions, 1985-1995 (Reel 132, Frame 677)
    - Budgets, 1975-1985 (Reel 132, Frame 687)
    - Budgets, 1986-1988 (Reel 132, Frame 877)
    - Budgets, 1989-1990 1989-1991 (Reel 133, Frame 1)
    - Budget, 1993 1993-1994 (Reel 133, Frame 354)
    - Budget, 1994 1993-1995 (Reel 133, Frame 650)
    - Budget, 1995 1994-1996 (Reel 133, Frame 911)
    - Budget, 1996 1994-1996 (Reel 134, Frame 1)
    - Budget, 1999 1997-1998 (Reel 134, Frame 183)
    - Estimated Excise Tax Calculation for, 2000 (Reel 134, Frame 308)
    - Eyrie Garden Sculpture, 1974-1980 (Reel 134, Frame 321)
    - General Ledger, Endowment Fund, 1989 (Reel 134, Frame 357)
    - General Ledger, General Fund, 1989 January-April (Reel 134, Frame 424)
    - General Ledger, General Fund, 1989 May-September (Reel 134, Frame 582)
    - General Ledger, General Fund, 1989 October-December (Reel 135, Frame 1)
    - General Ledger, Endowment Fund, 1993 (Reel 135, Frame 236)
    - General Ledger, General Fund, 1993 January-May (Reel 135, Frame 294)
    - General Ledger, General Fund, 1993 June-October (Reel 135, Frame 536)
    - General Ledger, General Fund, 1993 November-December (Reel 136, Frame 1)
    - General Ledger, General Fund, 1994 January-May (Reel 136, Frame 185)
    - General Ledger, General Fund, 1994 August-October (Reel 136, Frame 415)
    - General Ledger, General Fund, 1994 December (Reel 136, Frame 611)
    - General Ledger, General Fund, 1995 January-April (Reel 137, Frame 1)
    - General Ledger, General Fund, 1995 May-August (Reel 137, Frame 128)
    - General Ledger, General Fund, 1995 August-December (Reel 137, Frame 246)
    - General Ledger, General Fund, 1995 October-Closing (Reel 137, Frame 439)
    - General Ledger, General Fund, 1995 October-December (Reel 137, Frame 592)
    - General Ledger, 1996 March-July (Reel 137, Frame 688)
    - General Ledger, 1996 August-December (Reel 138, Frame 1)
    - General Ledger Listings, 1996 December 31 (Reel 138, Frame 220)
    - Monthly Account File, 1996 March (Reel 138, Frame 370)
    - Monthly Account File, 1996 April (Reel 138, Frame 378)
    - Monthly Account File, 1996 May (Reel 138, Frame 451)
    - Monthly Account File, 1996 June (Reel 138, Frame 530)
    - Monthly Account File, 1996 July (Reel 138, Frame 559)
    - Monthly Account File, 1996 August (Reel 138, Frame 596)
    - Monthly Account File, 1996 September (Reel 138, Frame 652)
    - Monthly Account File, 1996 October (Reel 138, Frame 695)
    - Monthly Account File, 1996 November, 1996-1997 (Reel 138, Frame 744)
    - Monthly Account File, 1996 December 9-1997 (Reel 138, Frame 782)
    - Monthly Account File, 1999 January, 1998-1999 (Reel 138, Frame 828)
    - Monthly Account File, 1999 February (Reel 138, Frame 886)
    - Monthly Account File, 1999 March (Reel 138, Frame 957)
    - Monthly Account File, 1999 April (Reel 138, Frame 1047)
    - Monthly Account File, 1999 May (Reel 139, Frame 1)
    - Monthly Account File, 1999 June (Reel 139, Frame 85)
    - Monthly Account File, 1999 July (Reel 139, Frame 175)
    - Monthly Account File, 1999 August (Reel 139, Frame 265)
    - Monthly Account File, 1999 September (Reel 139, Frame 365)
    - Monthly Account File, 1999 October (Reel 139, Frame 444)
    - Monthly Account File, 1999 November, 1999-2000 (Reel 139, Frame 549)
    - Monthly Account File, 1999 December, 1999-2000 (Reel 139, Frame 600)
  - Loans and Investments, 1984-1998; 2 (Reel 139, Frame 663)
    This series contains materials relating to PRI (program-related investing) that the Winthrop Rockefeller Foundation was involved in.
    - Program Related Investment (PRI), undated (Reel 139, Frame 664)
    - Arkansas Repertory Theatre Company, PRI, Loan Agreement, 1988 (Reel 139, Frame 670)
    - Arkansas Repertory Theatre Company, PRI, Correspondence, 1986-1998 (Reel 139, Frame 938)
    - Arkansas Repertory Theatre Company, PRI, Monthly Statement for Consortium of Banks, 1988 (Reel 140, Frame 1)
    - Arkansas Repertory Theatre Company, PRI, Monthly Statement for Winthrop Rockefeller Foundation, 1988 (Reel 140, Frame 102)
    - Arkansas Repertory Theatre Company, PRI, Deed of Release, 1998 (Reel 140, Frame 122)
    - Block Redevelopment, PRI, Cash Flow Reports for Auditors, 1988-1990 (Reel 140, Frame 124)
    - Block Redevelopment, PRI, Correspondence, 1984-1996 (Reel 140, Frame 134)
    - Block Redevelopment, PRI, Insurance, 1984-1995 (Reel 140, Frame 394)
    - Block Redevelopment, PRI, Marratt and Associates Real Estate, 1996-1997 (Reel 140, Frame 578)
    - Block Redevelopment, PRI, 7th Street Property-Closing, 1995-1997 (Reel 140, Frame 612)
    - Block Redevelopment, PRI, Tax Bill, 1984-1991 (Reel 140, Frame 793)
    - Delta Community Development Corporation, Incorporated, PRI, 1993-1995 (Reel 140, Frame 861)
    - Delta Community Development Corporation, Incorporated, PRI, Loan Agreement, 1993 (Reel 140, Frame 895)
    - Delta Community Development Corporation, Incorporated, PRI, Reports, 1995-1996 (Reel 140, Frame 979)
    - Philander Smith College, PRI, 1989-1992 (Reel 140, Frame 1000)
    - Philander Smith College, PRI, Loan Agreement, 1993 (Reel 140, Frame 1010)